<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on Amar Shavir</title>
    <link>https://itsrobel.tech/posts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on Amar Shavir</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 26 Jan 2023 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://itsrobel.tech/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>War on Morality</title>
      <link>https://itsrobel.tech/posts/deletion/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Jan 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://itsrobel.tech/posts/deletion/</guid>
      <description>History The issue of abortion has been a contentious and divisive one in American politics throughout history. The debate in the United States can be traced back to the 19th century, with the first laws regulating abortion being passed in the 1820s and 1830s. These early laws aimed primarily at protecting women&amp;rsquo;s health and restricting access to abortion only in cases where the procedure was deemed dangerous.
In the late 19th and early 20th century, the abortion debate became more politicized as various religious and medical groups took positions.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Orthodox christmas</title>
      <link>https://itsrobel.tech/posts/christmas/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Jan 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://itsrobel.tech/posts/christmas/</guid>
      <description>Intro While I typically like to write these kinds of pieces with as little emotional bearing as possible, the nature of my into the Orthodox Church is entirely personal to me. This piece will mostly go over the nuances of the Church from a westerner&amp;rsquo;s perspective and then any personal notes about the Church and the relationship I have with it after attending the Christmas service.
It is important to note that Orthodox Church that I attended was Eastern Orthodox of the Ethiopian people.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Things that make me irrationally angry</title>
      <link>https://itsrobel.tech/posts/anger/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Jan 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://itsrobel.tech/posts/anger/</guid>
      <description>Introduction In my last essay, I said I would keep everything as objective as possible. However, roughly four days ago, I realized this is my website, and I can say whatever I feel like without censorship. Although, I do have to keep in mind that because this is public, I will try to stay professionally subjective.
With that being said, here is a nice list of things that make me irrationally angry.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pythonic activies - tik tac toe</title>
      <link>https://itsrobel.tech/posts/python-scripts-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Dec 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://itsrobel.tech/posts/python-scripts-1/</guid>
      <description>A while ago during my first year of comp sci, I was tasked to create a game of tik tac toe. While not a complex procedure, I decided to make it more complicated for myself. In challenging my younger self, I went through 3 development phases.
The base game I do not have the files for the base game; if I find the Replit file, I will make sure to fill this section of the story.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>MLK</title>
      <link>https://itsrobel.tech/posts/mlk/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Sep 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://itsrobel.tech/posts/mlk/</guid>
      <description>Intro This essay was written for the MLK mentored program at the University of Louisville. I still believe in the topic and find it relevant. Doing research for this paper has opened my eyes to the ingrained tyranny the black community has faced, even from a religious standpoint. I have made some editorial changes for the essay to be more suitable for the blog but the main points and the majority of the text is largely untouched</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Development</title>
      <link>https://itsrobel.tech/posts/mythsandcommunity/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Aug 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://itsrobel.tech/posts/mythsandcommunity/</guid>
      <description>Introduction When writing, I am between the ages of seventeen and eighteen. Within all scientific and social metrics, I am still very much in my development. That said, please do not dismiss what I say; my words are the construct of experiences from the men who have gone before me and me.
Before I begin my long-formatted rant, I would like to share some of my stories to give an idea of where I come from, Ideologically and politically.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Create A Useless AI</title>
      <link>https://itsrobel.tech/posts/hollow/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Apr 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://itsrobel.tech/posts/hollow/</guid>
      <description>Introduction RoughlyRoughtly six months ago, I started on a journey. A journey journeyjourneyjourny of epic sword fights, great victories, and even more significant losses
For some context, my school partakes in a statewide program STLP The Program itself is a massive science fair/club; you can read more about it in the link above
The plan It was simple, make an app that is helpful to the student population The Idea Was to make an app for mental help; the goal was a Therapy app that students could download on their phones or access using our web page.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Minimum Wage</title>
      <link>https://itsrobel.tech/posts/minimum/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://itsrobel.tech/posts/minimum/</guid>
      <description>History The history of the minimum wage in the United States dates back to the early 20th century. The first federal minimum wage law, the Fair Labor Standards Act (FLSA), was passed in 1938 as part of President Franklin D. Roosevelt&amp;rsquo;s New Deal. The initial rate was set at 25 cents per hour and covered workers in specific industries, such as manufacturing and transportation.
In the years following the passage of the FLSA, the minimum wage was increased several times to keep pace with inflation.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Will</title>
      <link>https://itsrobel.tech/posts/angels/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://itsrobel.tech/posts/angels/</guid>
      <description>Introduction For as long as I can remember, I have been fascinated with the divine and their counterparts, whether they be demons, djins, or any other spiritual manifestation of power. While admittedly, they are a figment of my obsession with power, angels also serve as a foundation for the universe in a cosmological sense to maintain balance.
The Servants of Allah In Islam, angels are considered part of the unseen world and are believed to play a significant role in the daily life of a Muslim.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
