<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>politics on Robel Schwarz</title>
    <link>https://itsrobel.tech/tags/politics/</link>
    <description>Recent content in politics on Robel Schwarz</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 26 Jan 2023 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://itsrobel.tech/tags/politics/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>War on Morality</title>
      <link>https://itsrobel.tech/posts/deletion/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Jan 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://itsrobel.tech/posts/deletion/</guid>
      <description>History The issue of abortion has been a contentious and divisive one in American politics throughout history. The debate in the United States can be traced back to the 19th century, with the first laws regulating abortion being passed in the 1820s and 1830s. These early laws aimed primarily at protecting women&amp;rsquo;s health and restricting access to abortion only in cases where the procedure was deemed dangerous.
In the late 19th and early 20th century, the abortion debate became more politicized as various religious and medical groups took positions.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Minimum Wage</title>
      <link>https://itsrobel.tech/posts/minimum/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://itsrobel.tech/posts/minimum/</guid>
      <description>History The history of the minimum wage in the United States dates back to the early 20th century. The first federal minimum wage law, the Fair Labor Standards Act (FLSA), was passed in 1938 as part of President Franklin D. Roosevelt&amp;rsquo;s New Deal. The initial rate was set at 25 cents per hour and covered workers in specific industries, such as manufacturing and transportation.
In the years following the passage of the FLSA, the minimum wage was increased several times to keep pace with inflation.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
